快  快  你得再快点  伙计
Go. Go. You gotta go faster than that. Come on, man.
继续  这是违法的
Keep it going. Oh! That's illegal.
你比学校里吉姆发的快
You're faster than Jim at school.
我当然比学校里吉姆发得快
Of course I'm faster than Jim at school.
学校里那个吉姆是个垃圾
Jim at school is rubbish.
等等  等等
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
别作弊
No cheating here.
米娅
进展如何  安插好了吗
我要走了
I gotta go.
妈妈  亚当叔叔要去工作了
Mom, Uncle Adam's gotta go to work.
别用这个语气
Don't say it like that.
你是想让我心碎吗
What, are you trying to break my heart?
我得工作
Huh? It's working!
周二再来找你玩  好吗
I'm gonna see you on Tuesday, okay?
-好  -好吧
- Okay. - Yeah?
我爱你  小家伙
All right, I love you, pal.
要我给你打包点早餐吗
Want me to pack up some breakfast?
不用了  谢谢
No, I'm okay. Thanks.
一切都还好吧
Is everything all right?
嗯  不会有事的
Yeah. Yeah, it will be.
杰  伙计  醒醒
Jay. Hey, man. Wake up.
别紧张
Hey, it's all right. Whoa.
你没事吧
You okay?
You all right?
嗯  我就是想稍微睡一会
Yeah, man. I just came in to take a nap.
睡一会  现在是早上7点30分
A nap? It's 7:30 in the a.m., man.
你这么早来干什么
What are you doing here so early?
我要整理一些文件
I had to do some paperwork.
你确定你没事吗
Are you sure you're all right?
没事  伙计  只是...
Yeah, man. It was just...
做噩梦了
a bad dream.
南埃利斯街5490号需要警车支援
Need a car at 5490 South Ellis.
醉酒闹事  2221  你在附近吗
Drunk and disorderly. 2221, you close?
2221收到  正在过去
2221. 10-4, We're riding on it.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
1831  这起事故交给你们
1831, just threw one in your queue.
威克大道和威尔士街三车相撞
Handle the three-car pileup at Wacker and Wells.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋
其中一名司机已经送往医院
One of the drivers is being transported to Med.
我再派辆车进行交通...
I'll send another car for traffic--
不予受理  居民密码错误
Disregard. Incorrect pass code by resident.
翻译     H小欠   Lynn_宁   小萝莉   圈圈
21区各小组和市内其他小组注意
Units in 21 and units on the city-wide,
校对     圈圈
多起报警电话称目击到有人持枪
we have multiple calls of a man with a gun.
伦道夫公园  男性  黑人  一米六不到
Randolph Park. Male, black, 5'11",
时间轴     噃噃   chance-coco
身穿一件连帽衫和蓝色牛仔裤
wearing a hoodie and blue jeans.
我是G5021  继续向我告知情况
5021 George, hold me down on that.
后期     8T
便衣警察准备前往现场
Advise responding; plainclothes officer will be on the scene.
收到
Copy that.
总监     圈圈
-你开枪了吗  -没有开枪
- Hey! You got shots fired? - No shots fired.
-没看到他  -设立警戒线
- No eyes on him yet. - Get a perimeter set up.
要他继续派警车来
Tell him to keep the cars coming.
-明白  -快走  快走
- I got you. - Move, move, move.
我是5021G  人们正在从
5021 George. I've got people running
伦道夫公园大道1014号逃离
out of 1014 Randolph Park Ave.
-赶紧派支援过来  -收到
- Send me some help now! - Copy that.
他在哪里  他在哪里
Where is he? Where is he?
-上面  上面  -好  快去外面
- Up there, up there! - All right, go. Get outside!
我是5021G  枪手在二楼  伦道夫...
5021 George, shooter's on the second floor of 1014 Randolph--
-芝加哥警署  -警察  警察
- Chicago PD! - Police! Police!
守住出口
Take the exit!
我是5021G  紧急情况  有人受伤倒地
5021 George. Emergency. We got one down.
-派辆救护车来  -收到
- Roll an ambulance. - Copy that.
正在派救护车
Ambo on the way.
怎么样
How you doing?
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
疑犯跑了  根据情况分析
Offenders are in the wind. The way this went down,
肯定不止一人
there's gotta be more than one of them,
因为他不可能这么快躲过我
'cause he couldn't have got behind me that fast.
有几名受害人
How many victims?
一名  名叫特丽莎·马泰尔
One. Her name was Theresa Mattel,
是芝加哥中央大学的学生
she was a student at Central Chicago University.
警长  疑犯开了三枪
Sarge, the offender fired three rounds.
两枪打中胸口  一枪打中头
Two center mass, one head tap.
感觉不像是大规模枪击
Doesn't sound like a mass shooting.
是的  感觉不像
Yeah. It did not feel like one.
他使用了军用震爆弹  M84
He used a military stun grenade. M84.
你是第一名到现场的警探吗
Huh. You were the first detective on scene?
是的  我就在街角
Yeah. I was right around the corner.
好的  调取公园和大楼内的
Huh. All right. Start pulling footage from the park,
监控录像  查清楚
inside the building. Let's find out
-他们是从哪里来的  -警长
- where they were coming from. - Sarge.
有一名目击证人看到女性受害人
We have a witness who saw our female victim
带着一个孩子跑了进去
running inside with a kid.
她躲了起来  听到枪声  向上看去
She hid, heard gunshots, looked up,
看到疑犯架着一名男孩
and saw the offender running for an exit
从出口跑了出去
with a boy over his shoulder.
找到那个男孩了吗
Any sign of the boy?
那这是一起绑架事件吗
So this is a kidnapping?
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第七集
告诉我已经查到那个男孩的身份了
Tell me we got an ID on this boy.
还没有  不过对死者倒是查到了些信息
Not yet, but we do know more about the DOA.
她来自俄亥俄州代顿
She is originally from Dayton, Ohio.
生物专业  兼职做保姆
Biology major, worked part-time as a nanny.
我猜那个男孩是她照顾的孩子
So I assume the boy was under her watch.
我们在查她的手机
We're dumping her phone.
派人去她的宿舍了
Got a car on the way to her dorm.
当地警察正在去找她父母的路上
Local police are on the way to talk to her parents.
有线索表明死者就是
Anything that might make us think
凶手的目标吗
our DOA was the intended target?
没有  警长  似乎这些人
No. Sarge, it looks like these guys were there
就是为了绑架男孩  特里莎只是挡道了
to kidnap the boy, and Theresa just got in the way.
看
Look.
那是特丽莎和男孩
There's Theresa and the boy.
对
Right.
这是凶手
There's our shooter.
这是另一个凶手
There's our shooter's ghost.
这家伙进来就查看了所有的出口
When this guy comes in, he scans all the exits
似乎从来没进去过
like he's never been there before.
然后他就上楼接应了
Then he goes up as cover.
我觉得他们本来不想进去的
I don't think they meant to go in.
这只是个意外
I think this went wrong.
是特丽莎在公园看到他们  跑去保护男孩
Theresa saw them in the park and she ran to protect the boy,
结果自己被杀了
and it got her killed instead.
有可能  但毒枭那边有消息
It might be a long shot, but Narcotics has had a bead
说要绑架拿赎金
on a kidnapping and ransom crew they can't make.
我听说过  他们在抓
I heard about this. They're going after kids
和曼哈顿西区毒贩有关的孩子
connected to west-side dope gangs.
对  这伙人  他们绑架小孩
Right. The crew, they nab a kid,
要赎金  拿钱去买毒品
set ransom, banger pays them with drug money,
从没报过警
never calls the cops.
没有受害人  没有犯罪
No victim, no crime.
只有听说的消息
All they got is what they're hearing on the streets.
这伙人是三个男性  黑人  拉丁裔还有白人
Crew's three males. Black, Hispanic, white.
二十几岁  受过训练
20s, trained.
假设我们要找的人
I mean, if we're to assume
还有一个望风的司机  就都匹配上了
our guys had a getaway driver, it's a match.
去查
Dig into it.
-老大  -怎么
- Hey, boss. - Yeah.
我们查到孩子身份了  特丽莎的日程表里写
We ID'd the boy. Theresa's calendar says
她要接一个叫科迪·巴顿的孩子
she picked up a Cody Barton.
他之前在离伦道夫公园两个街区远的地方上音乐课
He was at a music lesson two blocks away from Randolph Park.
奥林斯基现在和孩子的妈妈在一起
Olinksy's on his way with the mom right now.
让卢戈封住媒体的口
Hey, tell Lugo keep a lid on this to the press.
如果有一伙人专职绑架
If there's a crew out there working a ransom,
我们可不想打草惊蛇
we don't want word of it to hit.
明白
Copy that.
对  是特丽莎
Yes, that's Theresa.
她帮我前夫开车  看孩子  但我...
She helps my ex-husband driving, babysitting, but I--
科迪的爸爸没有打来电话  周末科迪和他在一起
Cody's dad hasn't called. Cody was with him all weekend.
对  我们现在正在找你的前夫
Yeah, we're trying to track down your ex-husband right now.
能告诉我本是做什么的吗
Can you tell me what does Ben do for a living?
-他是个会计  -好
- He's an accountant. - Okay.
那么...特丽莎
So...Theresa--
死了吗
she's dead?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
很遗憾
Sorry.
艾米  你能想到什么可疑的人吗
Amy, can you think of anyone who might do this?
不  当然想不到
No. Of course not.
想不到谁会杀一个年轻姑娘
Not someone who would want to kill a young woman
带走我儿子
and take my son.
艾米  冷静点
Hey, Amy, please. Hey.
我需要你冷静
I want you to try to stay with me.
我再问你一个问题  好吗
Just one more question, okay?
你和本离婚的时候
When you and Ben were getting divorced,
有任何监护权上的问题吗
were there any custody issues?
没有
No.
本是一个糟糕的丈夫  但他是个好父亲
Ben was a terrible husband, but he is a good father.
科迪是我们之间唯一的共识
Cody's the only thing we ever agreed on.
这没道理啊
This doesn't make sense.
我们只是一个普通的家庭
We're just a normal family.
怎么会发生这种事
This can't be happening!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
本·巴顿  芝加哥警署  开门
Ben Barton! Chicago PD, open up!
钥匙和手机在桌上
Keys and cell phone are on the table.
老天
Oh, God.
看看这个
Take a look.
赶紧拿开
Get that away from me, man.
这个绑架勒索团伙貌似又绑架了一个孩子
Looks like this K&R crew just snatched another kid.
你说你要找我说藏匿屋的事
You said you needed to talk to me about a stash house.
我说谎了  雷...
I lied. Now, Rey...
我知道你侄子半年前被绑架了
I know your nephew was kidnapped six months ago.
我不想和你说这事  老兄
I am not talking to you about this, bro.
他们切下了孩子的手指
They sliced his finger off
把它放在纸箱里寄给了你的兄弟
and sent it to your brother in a cardboard box.
-拜托  -我不想说这事
- Come on, man. - I'm not talking to you about this!
这伙人又绑架了一个孩子
This crew just grabbed another kid.
告诉我他们是怎么办事的
Tell me how they work!
好吧  那我把抽屉里那个案子
Okay. How about I file that case
给立案侦查了如何
I got sitting in my drawer?
取消你的保释
Violate your parole? Huh?
放轻松点好吗
Relax, okay?
我兄弟接到了一个电话
My brother got a call.
他们说孩子在他们手上
They said they had his kid.
让他看看门口
They told him look on the porch.
布鲁诺的手指就在一个盒子里
It was Bruno's finger in a box.
他们给他48小时时间筹四十万
They gave him 48 hours to get 400K.
他们告诉他把钱放在哪
They told him where to place the cash, where to drop it.
那些混蛋拿了钱
Pricks got the cash.
就把布鲁诺放在高速旁
And they dropped Bruno off on the side of the highway.
他只记得其中一个人的手臂残了
All he remembers is that one of these guys had a messed up arm.
他说看起来他右手整条前臂
He said it looked like his whole right forearm
都被烧得不成样子  简直像化了似的
had been burnt up. Like it was melting away.
就这些了
And that's it, bro.
话说那几个团伙成员查得怎么样了
So what do we got on the crew?
这些人受过训练
Well, these guys are trained,
所以我查了查退伍军人系统
so ran a query through the VA.
一共有350名伤兵
There's 350 soldiers injured
有相似的年纪  体格和烧伤
with similar age, weight, and burn.
但只有四个住在芝加哥
But only four of them live in Chicago.
而只有一个非常匹配  路易斯·维嘉  28岁
And only one matches this well. That's Luis Vega, 28,
-曾在第一陆战营  -他去年被迫退役
- 1st Ranger Battalion. - Luis got booted last year
因为被路边炸弹炸伤  右前臂重伤
due to an IED injury. Right forearm burned through.
退役之后  他又在南美洲
After he got out, he spent three months
待了三个月  干雇佣安保
in South America on contract as security.
也就是绑架勒索
AKA, he did kidnapping and ransoms.
没错  身高体重都和这人完全吻合
Yep. Height and weight match this guy to a T.
-有人去找他了吗  -伪装车辆已经上路了
- We got someone headed to him? - Covert car en route.
-会监视他的  -很好
- We'll get eyes. - Good.
不过然后怎么办
Okay, but what's the plan, though?
因为我们手头的证据还不足以逮捕他
'Cause we can't grab him up on what we got,
而他开口招供的可能性很小
and odds of him talking are not good.
而且如果惊动了团伙成员  会害死那孩子的
Plus if we spook the crew, we could get this kid killed.
所以我们要马上监视路易斯
Well, that's why we get eyes on Luis right away.
你也可以派我去卧底
Or you put me under.
他当过突击队员  我们服役时间差不多
He was a Ranger. We served at the same time.
-我能和他说上话  -这主意不好
- I can connect with him. - That's a bad idea. No.
卧底只会更加激怒他
An undercover would only heat him up.
-我们的情报不够  -正是因为如此
- We don't have enough info. - That would be the point.
我来套情报
I'd get it.
老埃
Al?
你呢  你有看法吗  海莉
What about you? You got a take, Hailey?
不  我中立
No. I'm neutral.
那好  咱们试试看
Okay. Let's give it a shot.
鲁塞克会记录好一切
Ruzek will log everything.
我跟着你去现场
I'll stick by you in the field,
安东尼奥也会去现场以防万一
and Antonio will be there as a second.
就算你看不见我们  我们也能看着你
We'll have eyes on you even if you can't see us.
你为什么中立
Why the neutral?
最近有点担心
Just been a little concerned lately.
担心什么
About what?
担心你
About you.
你掩藏得挺严实  但我也不瞎  杰
You cover well, but I got eyes, Jay.
你确定你能行吗
You sure you're solid?
我们让
Yo. We just got
卧底缉毒警加速行动
the undercover narcotics up to speed.
我们的车跟踪路易斯到了面纱俱乐部
We got the coverts trailing Luis to the Veil Club.
那里的酒保是他妹妹  叫卡米拉
Bartender there named Camila. That's his sister.
行动吧
Let's roll.
要喝一杯吗
Can I get you a drink?
啤酒就行  随便上
Yeah. Just beer. You pick.
你看上那边那个柴杆儿老兄了吗
Hey, you like that scrawny dude over there?
那是我哥
Well, that's my brother.
他一般不这么随便出来晃
I mean, he doesn't usually swing that way,
不过我可以介绍介绍
but I can make an intro.
不用  啤酒就行了  多谢
No, just the beer is fine. Thanks.
你哥哥参过军吗
Was your brother in the Army?
是啊  突击队
Yeah, he was. Ranger.
我也是  我肯定在本宁堡见过他
Me too. I must have seen him at Benning.
好啊
Hoorah!
那是海军突击队的口号
That's the Marines.
路易斯
Hey, Luis.
-路易斯  这位是  -莱恩
- Luis, this is, uh... - Ryan.
我是75营的  军校第三突击队营
75th. 3rd Rangers out of Benning.
我肯定在那见过你
I must've seen you there, man.
我是06  07届最后才进去的
I was there the tail end of '06, '07.
-你在哪服役的  -哥们  我来只是
- So where'd you serve? - Hey, man. I just came here
喝个酒  不是跟人聊天的
for the drink, not to swap stories.
真是和善啊  他一直这样吗
That was so nice. Is he always like that?
混蛋样吗  九成九都是
A dick? Yeah. A solid 98% of the time.
我就是觉得肯定很有意思
I just thought it'd be fun.
多谢了
Thanks.
老兄  走路看着点
Yo, man. Watch where you're going.
怎么着  你有意见吗
What, you got a problem, tough guy?
你觉得呢
What you think?
你哥哥认识那几个人吗
Hey, does your brother know those guys?
-你挺能是吧  -怎么回事
- Oh, you a tough guy, huh? - What's going on?
婊子别多话  滚回去干活去
Bitch, get your ass back to the bar.
-你说什么  -冷静
- What'd you say? - Calm down.
我说滚回去干活  婊子
I said get back to the bar, bitch.
除非你想去我家耍耍
Unless you want to come to my house--
-想干什么都行  -你嘴巴放干净点
- You do whatever you want. - Hey, watch your mouth.
就不  你怎么着吧
What are you gonna do about it?
-想走吗  -咱们出去聊聊
- You wanna go? - Take it outside.
哥们
Yo, man!
-六点钟方向  -需要帮手吗
- Your six! - Need some help?
赶快走  不然警察来了
Get out of here before the cops come!
你没事吧  来吧  我扶着
You all right? Come on, I got ya.
服了四期  真厉害
Four tours? Damn, man.
你可真待得够久的
That's a lot of time in country.
回家的感觉怎么样
So what's it like being back home?
有工作吗
You working anywhere?
我做私人安保
I do private security.
我也是  你哪家的
Me too, man. Where you at?
打零工
Nothing formal.
给另一个老兵打下手
I just work for another vet.
她去哪儿了
Where the hell is she?
兄弟  那个老兵叫啥
Hey, man. Who's this other vet?
他还招人吗
And is he hiring?
我现在的工作  一小时才七块五
Look, my current job, I make 7.50 an hour.
我还得别个名牌  上面写着
And I gotta wear a frickin' nametag that says,
"嗨  我很友好的"
"Hi, I'm security friendly."
我们不招人的  实在抱歉
It's a small group. I'm sorry.
好吧
Yeah. Right on.
我钥匙丢了
I lost my keys.
你还好吗
Whoa! You all right?
谢谢你今天帮我
Thanks for having my back today, man.
就这样吗  你就上床睡觉了
That's it? You going to bed?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
到处乱看
Snooping.
-恶习不好改  -你在查看我的邮件
- It's a bad habit. - You going through my mail?
要么就是你没告诉我名字  要么就是我忘了
Either you didn't tell me your name or I forgot it, so...
所以没错  我就是在看你的邮件
Yeah, I'm goin' through your mail.
我不想引起你的反感
I was just trying to be smooth.
卡米拉·玛丽·维嘉
Camila Marie Vega.
连中间名都告诉我了啊
I even get the middle name.
我可不想你到处查
I don't want you digging around
我的出生证明
for my birth certificate.
你哥哥还好吗
Is, uh, your brother okay?
-他好像有点...  -醉了
- He seems a little-- - Wasted?
只喝酒吗
Just alcohol?
你说什么
Excuse me?
通常喝酒都会配点鸦片的
Well, usually it's alcohol and opiates, you know?
如果你一直都在干底层的活
If you're stuck at orange all the time,
只有鸦片才能让你重新找回自我
Oxy's the only that brings you back to white.
-让你平衡  -是让你麻木吧
- Evens you out. - Numbs you out.
不过还是谢谢你的观点
But thanks for your input.
抱歉  我不是想...
Sorry, I'm not trying to--
窥探  给我讲道理  你明明就是
Pry? Give me advice? Yeah, you are.
我只是有过这样的经历
I've just been there. That's all.
我过去七个月
I spent about seven months
不是在喝酒嗑药  就是在乱搞打架
doing nothing but drink, smoke, screw, fight.
你都是这么勾搭女人的吗
So is this how you usually hit on women?
怎么  不管用吗
What? It's not working?
你是怎么振作起来的
So how'd you get over it?
我也不知道
I got no idea.
我哥哥他...
Yeah, well my brother, he just--
他总是无法彻底振作
he hasn't come back all the way.
没有人可以吧
I don't think anybody ever does.
应该也就是...
I think you just kind of...
用其它的东西来填补已有的空缺
fill up whatever's missing with something else.
你需要帮助吗
You need some help?
霍斯特德狠揍了那家伙
Halsted caught that dude flush.
也就是个无辜的旁观者
Innocent bystander too.
他不是应该只打一拳的吗
Wasn't he only supposed to throw one punch?
可能吧  厄普顿说情况当时有点紧张
If that. Upton said it got a little hairy in there.
怪不得她那么生气
No wonder she was pissed.
那个卧底肯定气炸了
That undercover must be mad as hell.
那个好好撒玛利亚人要是发现
And that Good Samaritan's probably gonna sue
霍斯特德是个警察  估计要起诉了
when he finds out that Halsted was a cop.
你会把它删掉吧
You're gonna delete that, right?
当然  我不会把它存进去的
Of course. I'm not logging that.
媒体文件复制中
查到科迪他爸的线索了吗
All right, anything on Cody's dad?
还没  不过他经常
Not yet, but he likes to visit
-去银行  -好
- the bank a lot. - Okay.
他的记录显示他有很多
His finances show a hell of a lot
现金存款  总共九千
of cash deposits. All 9 grand,
正好低于上报门槛
so that's just under the federal threshold.
好  让安东尼奥和伯吉斯去联系他们的线人
All right, have Antonio and Burgess hit up their CIs.
肯定有人认识这个人
Someone in Players gotta know this guy.
收到
Copy that.
霍斯特德呢
And Halsted?
他没事
Uh...he's all good.
几个小时前他刚联系上路易斯
He actually just got in contact with Luis a few hours ago.
那就好
Good.
我是不是甩不掉你了
I ain't never gonna get rid of you, am I?
我说的话照办了吗
Do what I ask?
我问过本·巴顿的事了
Yeah, I asked my cousin about Ben Barton.
他给我们洗钱  但是做得不够好
He washes money for us. He ain't smart at it.
怎么说
How's that?
他一个月前亏了一百万美元
He lost a million about a month ago.
被什么餐厅的事给坑了
Got played on some restaurant thing.
那边那个人带着钱跑了
Guy on the other end ran off with the cash.
巴顿还活着
And Barton's still alive?
他把钱还上了
He paid the money back.
-他有那么多钱  -反正那个时候有
- He's got that kind of cash? - He did till then.
你是说他现在破产了
You saying he's broke now?
他一个小时前给我兄弟手底下的人打了电话
He called one of my cousins' people about an hour ago.
厄奈斯托  想找他借50万
Ernesto. He asked to borrow 500 grand.
本·巴顿  坐下
Ben Barton. Sit down.
我说过我要是跟警察说话的话他们会杀了科迪
I told you they'd kill Cody if I talked to cops.
听我说  没事的
Hey, listen to me. It's all right.
没人知道你在这里
Nobody knows you're here.
我只想让我的儿子回来
I just want to get my son back!
我们也是
So do we.
我们知道你在为黑帮洗钱  这我们不管
We know you wash money for gangs, we don't care.
至少现在不管
Not now, anyway.
我只是想尽力而为  可是我破产了
Look, I'm trying to do what I can, but I'm broke.
我连一百块都凑不出来
I can barely scrape together 100 grand,
而且没有一个朋友愿意帮我
and none of my associates are willing to help!
好吧  他们要多少钱
All right. How much did they ask for?
一百万
$1 million!
那人说给我48小时  不然他就崩了科迪
The man said I had 48 hours or he'd shoot Cody in the head.
你什么时候接到电话的
What time did you get the call?
昨天下午两点
Yesterday. 2 p.m.
好的  我们还有26个小时  听我说
All right, we got 26 hours. Listen to me.
我们会竭尽所能
We will do everything in our power
帮你救出你儿子
to help you save your son.
但你也得帮我们
But you gotta help us.
-你怎么样啊  -我还好
- How you holding up, man? - I'm okay.
等一下  我接个电话  对
Hold on, let me get this. Yeah.
你的手怎么样
How's your hand?
没事  我做对了
It's fine. It was the right move.
你是做了  但我不确定是对的
Yeah. It was a move. I'm not sure if it was right.
我把能找到的路易斯的资料都调出来了
Pulled everything I could find on Luis.
精神病史  医疗情况  详细的都在报告上
Psych history, medical, details on ops.
增兵时期去了伊拉克服役
Served in Iraq during the surge.
卡林哥山谷  08年  可能见过...
Korengal Valley, '08. Probably saw some--
我也去过那里  我知道他看到了什么
I did a tour there too. I know what he saw.
你跟卡米拉说了你是什么时候回来的
So that stuff you told Camila about when you got back.
是真的吗
Is that true?
好的  再联系  好的
All right, talk to you later. All right, man.
安东尼奥的电话
This number's Antonio.
他会去跟卢戈谈谈
He's talking to Lugo,
试试看搞到九十万  这样我们才能行动
trying to get his hands on 900K so we can make the drop.
我们需要你找到这些人
We need you to ID these guys.
这些是山寨货吗
Are these lookalikes?
你想让我给路易斯真的毒品吗
You want me to give Luis actual drugs?
我们应该都知道这是违法的吧
I'm assuming we all know that's illegal.
我们需要尽快搞定这事  得靠这个
We need an easy in. This is it.
一定要关掉警用设备
Just make sure your wire's off.
你好啊  卡米拉在家吗
What's up, man? Is Camila home?
不在  上班去了
No. Working.
真的吗  我们说好见面的
Really? We were gonna hang out.
是的  她准备帮我庆祝  我被开除了
Yeah, she was gonna help me celebrate. I got fired.
我显然不够友好
Apparently, I'm not friendly enough.
你知道她几点会回来吗
Um...you know what time she's coming back?
你介意我在这里等她一下吗
You mind if I stick around, wait for a while?
我介意
Yeah, I do mind.
我一直很尊重你
I've been very respectful.
你是军人  哥们
You're a soldier, bro.
我知道你见过什么  做过什么
I know what you've seen, done.
我妹妹的人生
My sister don't need
不需要再多一个这样的人
another person like that in her life, you know?
好吧  如果你这么想
All right, if that's how you feel,
那我走呗
I'll back off, man.
好的
All right.
对了
Yeah, um...
你想喝酒吗
You want a drink, man?
想来几杯吗  我有一瓶伏特加
You wanna have a few shots? I got a bottle of vodka.
陪我庆祝一下  拜托
Help me celebrate. Come on.
我去  西蒙斯他有...
Damn, man. Simmons with the uh...
有面部抽搐症  是的
With the face tic, yeah.
真不敢相信那家伙过去了
I can't believe that guy made it in country.
他还活着回来了  很多人没有
He made it out, too. A lot of people didn't.
很多死了的人都不是军人  知道吗
Hell of a lot that died that didn't sign up, you know?
孩子  女人
Kids, the women.
孩子最可怜了
Yeah, kids are the worst.
我还是会看到  那个八岁的小女孩
I still see this, uh... this eight-year-old girl.
做噩梦梦到她  漂亮的脸蛋  黝黑的皮肤
I have nightmares about her. Beautiful face, dark skin.
-八岁  -嗯
- Eight? - Mm-hmm.
真小
That's young.
是的  我的子弹  打穿了一个士兵
Yeah. My nine, it went through a combatant,
穿过一扇门
and then it went through a doorway,
打中了她的脖子
and it ripped open her neck.
但她没有马上死掉
She didn't die right away, though.
我如果慢一点  就能看到她了
Now, if I slow down, I see her.
我都看到了  我看到山谷
And I see all of it. I see the valley.
看到孩子  狗
I see the kids, dogs.
我这里是一个十七岁的孩子
For me it's a 17-year-old.
那孩子跟我们走得很近
Kid used to kick it with us.
镇上的头头用炸弹炸死了他
Town leaders killed him with an IED.
然后大家都不想碰他
Nobody wanted to touch him after,
所以我把他的肢体聚到一起  用垃圾袋
so I scooped up the pieces. Used a trash bag.
他们会永远在我们的脑海里
Ain't never gonna leave us, man.
你朋友瑞安来了
Hey. Your friend Ryan is here.
他说他跟你约好了
He said he was supposed to meet you.
好的
Okay.
回见
See you then.
你今晚跟卡米拉约了见面吗
You were supposed to meet Camila tonight?
在家吗
At the apartment?
为什么她不知道
How come she didn't know that?
因为我没告诉她
'Cause I didn't tell her.
我本来准备突然袭击
Man, I was gonna show up.
表现得脆弱而迷人  她肯定喜欢
Be all vulnerable, charming. She was gonna love it.
最后却对着你个猪头
I ended up talking about all this depressing crap
说这些丧气事
with your ugly ass.
我得走了
I should get going, though.
如果你需要什么东西
Look, man. If you ever need something to like
放松一下  我可以帮你
take the edge off, I got you covered.
-是吗  -对
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
用什么帮
With what?
现在我身上只有些羟二氢可待因酮
Right now all I got on me is some Oxy.
是吗  多少钱
Yeah? How much you want for it?
不用了  兄弟  我请你
No, man. It's on the house.
如果你能帮我搞定那私人安保的工作  兄弟
If you set me up with your private security buddy.
你知道我不是真的做私人安保的吧
You know I don't really do private security, right?
兄弟  我不在乎
Man, I don't care.
我只是需要一份工作  找点刺激
I just need a job. Some excitement.
否则我会疯的  拜托
I'm gonna lose my damn mind. Come on.
好  好  好  好  成交
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. Deal.
好
All right.
都是假钱
It's a burn bag.
这是我能做到的极限了  汉克
Best I can do, Hank.
卢戈已经批准用1505资金了
Yeah, well Lugo already approved the 1505 funds.
那是他做了个错误的决定
Well, he made a mistake.
自从新的改革方案实施以来
Since the new reform package went through,
所有用钱的要求都要由我批准
all requests for cash run through me.
遗憾的是我刚批了70万给缉毒组
Unfortunately, I just signed off 700K to Narcotics.
丹尼  听我说
Denny, listen to me.
如果我带着一袋子假钱去见这些人
If I go to these people with a bag full of phony cash,
他们把那孩子杀了的
they're gonna kill this child.
你知道我建议你慢慢来的
You know I suggest you slow down--
他们手里有一个8岁的孩子
There's an eight-year-old boy out there!
你就这么自负
You come in here with your ego?
你他妈是不是有病
The hell is wrong with you?
我给缉毒组的70万
This 700K that I gave to Narcotics,
那笔钱会用到贩毒集团那
that money's going to a cartel buy
拿下三个头目
that's gonna take down three bosses--
他们中的每一个  身上都背着很多条人命
each one of them wanted on multiple murders!
更不用说那些我们清除掉的街上的毒品
Not to mention the dope we'll get off the street!
那些造成246个人吸毒过量死亡的毒品
Dope that has caused 246 ODs!
所以钱要花在那里
So that is where the cash is going.
我也希望我们还有90万可以支配  但是我们没有
I wish we had another 900K sitting around, but we don't!
我知道你有下属卧底在里面  你得知道...
I know you've got a guy under. You just have to figure out--
我知道了  你说得很清楚了
I got it. You made your point.
怎么了  你是在等我说谢谢还是等我说对不起
What, are you waiting around for a thank you or a I'm sorry?
你等不到的
'Cause it ain't coming.
所以你该走了
So you should probably go.
你他妈怎么进来的
How the hell did you get in here?
既然你不给我开门  就让你邻居放我进来了啊
The neighbor buzzed me in since you didn't.
你今早应该出现的
You were supposed to swing by this morning.
-计划有变  -不  兄弟  我们做了交易
- Yeah, well thing's changed. - No, man. We made a deal
我已经做到我要做的了
and I already gave you my end.
你要求的我也会做到的  但不是现在
And you'll get your end too, but not now.
不  哥们  没这么做事的
No, man. That's not how it's gonna work.
得按说好的办  所以到底是怎么回事
A deal's a deal. So what's up?
你已经把你的意思说的很清楚了  兄弟
You made your damn point already, man.
-我不需要根链子...  -你他妈是谁
- I don't need a leash-- - Who the hell are you?
是我的哥们瑞安  他只是顺路过来
It's my boy Ryan. He was just stopping by.
我们一起在佐治亚州本宁堡待过  他是个突击队员
We were at Benning together. He's a Ranger.
你觉得今天是约会的
And you thought today would be a good day
好日子吗
to have a little date?
我们走了
We're gonna go.
好了  开始吧
Okay. Here we go.
好
Okay.
V73NA46
Victor, seven, three, Nora, Andy, four, six.
9M1W
And nine, Mary, one, William,
X51
x-ray, five, one.
好了  第一个牌照登记在乔什·米勒名下
Okay, first plate is registered to a Josh Miller.
28岁  没有前科
28. No priors.
第二个牌照在马库斯·泰特名下  25岁
Second plate is Marcus Tate. 25.
身高体重和我们的大学枪手匹配
Height and weight match our college shooters.
近两年他两次酒后驾驶
He's got two DUIs and an assault charge
还被以人身攻击罪起诉过
in the last two years.
脾气不好的家伙  我们可以利用这点
Angry guy. We could use something there.
马库斯是前军队步兵
Marcus is former Army Infantry
乔什以前是海军突击队的
and Josh is a Marine vet.
就是他们
We got them.
-你想让我们抓马库斯  -对  如果你们抓了他
- You want us to pull Marcus? - Yeah, if you guys pull him,
我就能说服路易斯让乔什用我
I can get Luis to get Josh to use me.
你让他出局  我就能进去了
You get him out, I'm in.
-不行  -不行  那是什么意思
- No. - No? What the hell does that mean?
意思是太危险了
It means it's too risky.
当局者迷  你相信这个家伙
You're not seeing straight. You trust this guy,
但是你不应该相信他  你在俱乐部里做得出格了
and you shouldn't. You went offline at the club,
-你打了一个平民  -我没有别的选择
- you punched a civilian. - I didn't have a choice.
-你有  -好了  好了  够了
- Yes, you did. - All right, all right, enough.
好  我们把马库斯抓起来
Okay. We pull Marcus.
警长
Sarge.
这是唯一的办法  海莉
This is our only play, Hailey.
好了  讨论结束
Okay. We're done talking.
你知道你不应该在白天
You know you should never come to this place
来这里的  对吗
in the daytime, right?
没有"化妆"看起来不太好
It doesn't look good without makeup.
等等  "化妆"是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean makeup?
一群人在烟雾缭绕
Hundred people in a drug haze.
是啊  这里的确很令人抑郁
Oh yeah, it's definitely depressing in here.
听说你最近和我哥在一起
Heard you've been hanging with my brother.
是啊  我们在谈论工作方面的事
Yeah, we're talking a few work type things.
你知道在哪能找到他吗
Do you know where I could find him?
所以你才来这里
Oh, that's why you're here.
有那么一秒  我以为你是来找我的
For a second, I thought it was for me.
不  我是来找路易斯的  抱歉
Nope, it's all about Luis. Sorry.
太伤心了
Ouch.
好吧  你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
实际上一半为了路易斯一半为了你
Actually it's 50% Luis and it's 50% you.
但只是私底下和你说
But just between you and me,
他并不想看到你和前突击队员约会
he's not excited about you hanging out with an ex-Ranger.
所以
So...
我自己的决定自己做
Yeah, well, I make my own decisions.
但我需要和他聊聊
I do need to talk to him, though.
你知道哪儿能找到他吗
Do you know where I could find him?
这就是你的回应
That's your response?
抱歉  一个美女给了我一个
I'm sorry, I say really stupid things
出其不意的吻  而我却说了很蠢的话
when beautiful women kiss me out of the blue. You're right.
去威尔士那儿的多纳休酒吧看看
Try Donahue on Wells.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么鬼  你现在是在跟踪我吗
What, are you stalking me now?
不  你妹妹说你会在这里
No, man. Your sister said you'd be here.
你怎么了  看着很糟
What's wrong with you? You look terrible, man.
没事  我...
It's fine, I--
我的老板急疯了
My boss is freaking.
第三个人临时走了
Third guy apparently left town.
而一个小时后就要干活
They got a job in an hour.
太好了  告诉他可以用我
That's great, man. Tell him to use me.
-他不会用你的  -你又不知道
- He's not gonna use you. - You don't know that.
他一定会想用我的
He's gonna want to use me over nobody.
好吗  他都不用改变战略计划
Right? He's not gonna want to change his tact plan.
你只要说服他就好
All you gotta do is convince him.
而且你看上去很不想
And you sure as hell don't look like you want to do
只和他搭档干活
whatever this is with just him.
我们有过一样的训练经历
Now we've had the same training,
你知道我会为你做好掩护的
so you know I'm gonna have your back.
和其它的行动一样
It's gonna be like any other op.
如果你不想独自去  就别独自去
If you don't want to go in alone, don't.
-我不是从杰克那儿认识他的  -我认识就行了
- I don't know him from Jack. - I do.
你认识有什么用
You think that that means something?
不带上他就拉倒  你想要3双眼睛吗
Man, it's him or nothing. You want six eyes?
你们可以为我争吵
Look, you guys can keep arguing about me,
也可以告诉我想要怎样
or you can tell me what you want.
我是过来帮忙的  行不行给个准话
I'm here to do you a favor. Tell me yes or no.
我不想浪费时间
I'm not gonna waste my time.
他不想浪费时间的
He's not gonna waste his time.
好  你想知道计划
Okay. You want the plan?
我打个电话  我们就行动
I'm gonna make a call, then we're gonna go.
是个简单的安保工作  得到我们需要见的
It's a simple security job. Gonna get a location,
对方的位置和照片就行
a photograph of the man we're gonna meet,
始终瞄准他的额头
You keep a bead on his forehead the whole time.
我告诉你撤的时候你就撤
When I say it's time to leave, you leave.
觉得你能搞定吗
Think you can handle that?
可以
Yeah, I can handle it.
责任你担着
This is on you.
就是这些吗
Is that all he's gonna tell me?
他要告诉我的就这些吗
That's all he's gonna tell me?
-不会有事的  -开玩笑吧
- You'll be fine. - Are you kidding me?
这是什么  你在干嘛
What is that? What are you doing?
-是一粒药  -不不  老兄
- It's one pill. - No! No, man.
不不  不能这样
No, no, no, no. This is not happening.
我会和你一起行动  好吗
I'm gonna do this thing with you, all right?
但你头脑不清楚的时候
But I'm not going in there blind
我不会盲目地和你行动
with you jammed out of your mind,
所以告诉我一些细节
so tell me something. Give me some details, man.
我不能告诉你
I can't give you any details, man.
-告诉我这活儿到底是什么  -不能
- Tell me what the job is! - I can't!
我和你没有利益冲突  拜托
I'm useless to you! Come on!
好  这是绑架勒索  好吗
Fine, it's a K&R, all right?
孩子不在这里  我们只是去拿钱
Kid's elsewhere. We're just picking up the money.
-就这么简单  -你们绑架了人
- Simple. - You kidnapped somebody?
-小声点  -你...
- Hey, lower your voice! - Are you--
这是简单的好活儿
It's fine. Simple.
不会有什么把我们牵扯其中
There's not one thing linking any of this to us.
孩子被关着  我不知道在哪里
The kid's being held. I don't know where.
在乔什的人那儿  我不知道是谁
With one of Josh's connects, I don't know who.
那家伙都没联系电话  好吗
Guy doesn't even have a phone, all right?
我不会这么说的
There's no way in hell I'm saying that!
这是我们最好的...
Listen, this is our best--
是我们唯一的机会
This is our only shot.
我知道你们都不了解我
Look, I know neither of you know me,
但你们可以信任我
but you can trust me.
这是我的工作职责
This is what I do for a living.
我失去了儿子
Look, I lost my son.
我保证我会尽全力
And I promise you I'm doing everything I can
确保你不会这样
to make sure you don't.
-喂  -现在你要开到格兰特公园
- Hello? - Right now, you're gonna drive to Grant Park.
密歇根和第八大道交口
Michigan and Eighth Street.
在转角  你会看到一个红色的垃圾桶
On the corner, you're going to see a red trash can.
你走过去  把钱丢进去
You walk to that can, you put the money in that can,
就离开
and you walk away.
接着开车回家
You get in your car, and you drive home.
按我们说的做  我们就会放了你儿子
You follow these instructions, and we will release your son.
懂吗
Do you understand?
懂吗  本
Do you understand me, Ben?
不
No!
不  我什么都不会给你
No, I'm not giving you anything.
我什么都不会给你
I'm not giving you a damn thing.
我要报警
I'm calling the police!
操
God!
我问你  如果这生意黄了
Let me ask you something, if he axes this,
他会撕票吗
does he kill the kid?
我们做过  不会...
We've done this before, all right? It's--
不要告诉我不会有事
Don't tell me it's fine!
他会杀了这个孩子  是吗
He's gonna kill this kid, isn't he?
听着  如果需要我
Listen, if I gotta convince you
说服你应该怎么办
where you need to be on this,
那就这样  我们不杀这个孩子
then so be it! We are not killing a kid!
我们要阻止这件事  明白了吗
We're gonna stop this, do you understand me?
我们无法阻止  我不知道孩子在哪里
We can't stop it. I don't know where the kid is.
即使我知道  如果不是乔什
Even if I did, anyone who goes through that door
任何人经过那扇门  都会被击毙
that's not Josh, they're getting shot.
那又如何  那又如何
So what? So what?
我们经过过多少门
How many doors have we gone through?
不能再死孩子了  我不能再背上一个孩子的命
Not another kid, man. I can't carry another kid.
你能吗
Can you?
路易斯
Luis!
不不不  不是你  你留在那
No, no, no. Not you. You stay there!
-任务结束了  -什么
- The mission's over. - What?
-结束了  -那...
- It's over. - So, what--
-你知道  -我们要把人都杀了吗
- You know it is. - So we gotta kill everyone?
我不想把人都杀了
I don't want to kill everyone, man.
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
干什么
Why?
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
把你的枪给路易斯
Now give Luis your gun.
我才不会把我的枪给你
Hey--hey, I'm not giving you my gun.
放松  我们只是去转一下
Relax, we're just going for a ride.
我才不会把枪给你  路易斯
I'm not giving you my gun, Luis.
-闭嘴  -你不会拿到的
- Shut up, man. - You're not getting it, man.
瑞安  把枪给我
Ryan, give me your gun.
你知道会发生什么
You know what's about to go down.
把你的枪给我  上车
Give me your gun. Get in the damn car.
下车
Get out.
我不下车
I'm not getting out of the car.
你不下的话我们就把你弄下去
You get out, or we get you out.
我们得把他绑起来  来
We gotta tie him up, come on.
这里有监控  那里就有摄像头
He's got this place wired up. There's a camera right there.
他可能已经知道我们来了
He probably already knows we're here.
那我们就快点行动  我掩护你
All right, then we move fast. I got your back.
掩护
Cover.
行动
Move.
跟紧  跟紧  小心
Stay on me. Stay on me. Watch out.
我要妈妈
I want my mom!
掩护
Cover!
我是警察  我救你出去
Police officer. Let's get you out of here.
快  走
Come on, let's go!
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
瑞安
Ryan!
路易斯
Luis!
干掉他
Take him down!
没事了
You're okay.
快啊
Come on!
杰
Jay.
快啊
Come on.
杰
Jay!
不
No!
-没事  -他真的没事
- I got it. - He's really okay!
-他真的没事吗  -他没事
- He's really all right? - He's fine.
我不知道怎么...我欠你的
I don't know how I can ever--I owe you!
现在你什么都不欠我
You don't owe me anything right now.
我们以后再说
We'll talk about all that later.
-去看你儿子吧  本  -妈妈  爸爸
- Go see your son, Ben. - Mom! Dad!
嗯
Yeah.
-局里见  -好
- See you back at the district? - Yeah.
到此为止了
This is it, okay?
虽然没有装上窃听器  但那里的东西
I couldn't get the bug planted, but that right there--
足够起诉滥用职权了
it's enough for a case of official misconduct,
所以你跟我两清了
so you and me, we're good.
你告诉我我们两清了
You're gonna tell me when we're good?
你要求的事我都做了  所以是的
I've done everything you've asked, so...yeah!
放过我姐姐吧
Just let my sister off the hook.
拜托
Please.
你这样的年轻人在汉克·博伊特身边
Young people like you hang around Hank Voight
待久了  就开始觉得他是真正的警察
long enough, you start thinking he's real police.
老套  硬气  无敌
Old timer. Tough. Invincible.
影响到你了  是吧
Rubs off on you a bit, huh?
你觉得是谁教他那样做的
Who in the hell do you think it is taught him to be that way?
你不许再那样跟我说话
You don't talk to me like that ever.
你和我还没有两清
And you and me are not good.
我说两清才两清
Until I say we are.
海莉·厄普顿来电
你听说了吗  我不明白
Did you hear? I mean, I don't understand.
这一切都说不通啊  警察说
None of it makes sense. The police said
他们跟一个人一起...
they were with some guy and they were--
节哀  节哀
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
你在场吗
Were you there?
瑞安
Ryan!
我不在
No, I wasn't.
进来  瑞安
Come in, Ryan.